tollywood24.com 2017-12-15

# Privacy Policy - tollywood24

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

Sites like Google AdSense, Google Analytics, FeedBurner, Flickr or [other third-party services](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) may place and read cookies or use web beacons to collect non-personal information. These services use the data to track conversions, to show statistics about this site or to improve their features.

[Cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) are small pieces of data that reside on your computer and can only be read by the sites that placed them. You can [disable cookies](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1), [manually clear them](http://www.aboutcookies.org/default.aspx?page=2) and [control which cookies are allowed](http://www.aboutcookies.org/default.aspx?page=1).

To find more, read [Google's privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html), [Yahoo's privacy policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/) and the privacy policies of [the third-party services](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) accepted by Google AdSense.

The ads from this site are served by Google AdSense, a third-party service that shows contextually-targeted ads, placement-targeted ads and interested-based ads. Google uses the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) to serve ads based on the sites you have recently visited. You can go to the [Google Ads Preferences page](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) to opt out of the DoubleClick cookie.

 **Contact Information**

If you have any questions or concerns please contact us at [admin@tollywood24.com](mailto:admin@tollywood24.com) . This privacy policy updated March 2014.
